Where can we go from His presence?
Where can we go from His presence? Nowhere!
It is time now for His blessing to locate you.
[Amen!]
Listen, you have been positioned already.
You have been positioned. - [Amen]
You must believe what I am saying because this is not my word - not mine! Not mine!
You have been positioned! - [Amen]
For healing! - [Amen]
For blessing! - [Amen]
For deliverance! - [Amen]
For salvation! - [Amen]
Right now, begin to receive it!
Viewers all over the world, begin to receive it!
Receive them right now, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to receive them!
His mercy - you have been positioned!
You have been positioned for His mercy!
His favour - you have been positioned for His favour! - [Amen]
Receive it right now.
I have been positioned for His favour.
I have been positioned for His mercy!
His favour, His mercy - Lord Jesus, in Jesus Christ's name! - [Amen]
I command healing on you! - [Amen!]
Wherever affliction, disease or sickness located - be healed! - [Amen]
Be removed! - [Amen]
Where can affliction go? Where can disease go?
In your organ - there is no hiding place.
In your blood - be healed! - [Amen]
In your bone - be healed! - [Amen]
I can see you being healed! - [Amen!]
I can see you being delivered! - [Amen!]
I can see!
Remember, physical eyes can see the present darkness but the eyes of faith can see the light.
I can see! - [Amen!]
Physical eyes can see the present darkness, your situation, the sickness, disease
but the eyes of faith can see the light. - [Amen]
Be free, in Jesus' name! - [Amen!]
Be free! - [Amen!]
You are free. - [Amen]
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus's Name
Listen, the devil must remove his hand. - [Amen!]
Listen, Jesus is involved; devil you must remove your hand! - [Amen!]
When Jesus is involved, devil, remove your hand!
Remove your hand!
[Amen!]